hiphopgame.com 2011-12-15

# Exclusive Hip Hop News, Audio, Lyrics, Videos, Honeys, Wear, Sneakers, Download Mixtapes

Thank you for visiting the **HipHopGame** web site and reviewing our privacy policy.  Our policy is simple: we collect no personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us.  We do not give, share, sell, or transfer any personal information to a third party. _ ****_ **Non-Personal Information We Record**

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the web site, read pages, or download information, our web site's operating system will automatically record some general information about your visit.

 _ ****_ **During your visit, our web operating system will record:**

1\. The Internet domain for your internet service, such as "xschool.edu", if you connect from a school or other educational institution, or "xcompany.com" if you connect using a private Internet access account.

2.  The type of web browser (such as "Netscape version x" or "Internet Explorer version x") that you are using.

3.  The type of operating system that you use (such as Macintosh, Unix, or Windows).

4.  The date and time you visit our site, and the web pages that you visit on our site.

5.  The address of the previous web site you were visiting, if you linked to us from another web site.

We use this information for statistical analysis, to help us make our site more useful to visitors.  Our system does not record personal information about individuals.

 _ ****_ **Information from E-mail You Send to Us  
**  
If you decide to send us an electronic mail message (e-mail), the message will usually contain your return e-mail address. If you include personally-identifying  information in your e-mail because you want us to address issues specific to your situation, we may use that information in responding to your question.  Please be aware that most e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. Please send only information necessary to help us respond to your question. _ ****_ **Information Collected from Interactive Forms  
**  
We ask you to voluntarily submit personal information (such as your e-mail address, name, occupation, etc.) on our question submission form.  That information is used solely to help us answer your question as best we can, or (rarely) to contact you if we have technical problems responding to your question.  The information is not made available to any third party. _ ****_ **Site Security and Intrusion Detection  
**  
For security purposes and to make sure this service remains available to all users, our web operating system collects information that could help identify someone making unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise damage this website.

Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we make no other attempts to identify individual users or their usage habits. We only use raw monitoring data logs for determining trends in usage patterns and in diagnosing systems problems.  
**  
**

_****_**Links to Other Sites  
**  
Our policy discloses the privacy practices for the HipHopGame web site, but HipHopGame does provide links to other web sites. When you leave the HipHopGame Web site (http://www.hiphopgame.com), you will be going to sites that are beyond our control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. The privacy policies and procedures described here for HipHopGame do not apply to any external links. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any site you link to from ours, especially if you share any personal information.

If you have questions about HipHopGame's privacy policy or other questions about our site, feel free to email us.
